Office of Community Relations Records UA233
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Office of Community Relations Records
1970 -- 2016
1921 -- 2018
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Government and Community Relations
Rubel, Barbara
UA233
20.28 Linear Feet 18 record cartons, 3 letter size document boxes, 1 12" LP box, and 2 oversize folders
This collection contains records created by the Office of Community Relations, including information on Tufts campus buildings, projects, and surrounding neighborhoods.
Conditions Governing Access
University records are closed for 20 years from the date of their creation. Records older than 20 years that do not pertain to student education, staff and faculty employment and Board of Trustees records are open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by the Office of Community Relations, 2013-2018.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged in three series: Project files; Subject files; and Campus files.
Biographical / Historical
The Office of Community Relations was formed in the late 1970s during a series of reorganizations of the University Development administration. For the 1978-79 academic year, the position of "Director of Public/Community Relations" was created, and held by the previous Director of Public Information, Harry B. Zane. After Zane's resignation in 1979, the position remained unfilled for the next two years. In 1981, Barbara Rubel was appointed as Director of Community Relations; Rubel retired in 2018.
The reorganization of the Development administration arose under the leadership of Dr. Thomas Murnane, appointed in 1979 to the position of Vice President of University Development. In 1979, Murnane made a point of expanding and restructuring every area of the University Development Division, such that 66% of Development staff started that year. Murnane had been appointed to fulfill the long-term goals of improving relations with the local Medford and Somerville community, as well as increasing capital raised for the university. Relations had been rocky with the communities since the 1960's, due to an expansion in Tufts' enrollment that resulted in a wealthier, more selective student body. Additionally, over-enrollment with the class of 1981 resulted in a university deficit, creating a need for capital to be raised.
During its formative years, the Office of Community Relations made an effort to improve access to Tufts resources for the Medford and Somerville Community. Starting in 1977, Tufts participated in the Comprehensive Employment and Training Act, which provided summer employment to local Somerville and Medford high school students. In the early 1980's, Tufts also began a program for Medford and Somerville public high school teachers and students to take classes at Tufts; students could audit classes for high school credit for no cost, and teachers could take summer classes at a half-tuition discount.
The department also volunteered Tufts University in 2004 as a partnering agency with the Medford Public Schools in the 21st Century Community Learning Centers Grant Program. Though Tufts assumed no financial liability in the signing, it pledged to use grant money to provide its resources to the Medford community. Per this agreement, Tufts recruited students to staff various programs, operated after school sites for the Tufts Literary Corps, and provided the Kids to College program to Medford sixth graders.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains records created or collected by the Office of Community Relations, an office within the University Relations Division. The collection includes project files, subject files and campus files. Project files include construction and architecture plans and maps; proposals; permits and licenses; studies and reports; correspondence; publicity and neighborhood communications; and files on committees, including meeting minutes and agendas. Subject files include information on Tufts buildings; policies; committees and associations within and outside Tufts; events and programming within Tufts and within neighborhood communities; construction projects; and Tufts presidents. Campus files include information relating to financial support for each campus; events and programs sponsored by Tufts to engage the local community; letters and requests from neighborhood residents; information relating to city and local governments; historical information on each neighborhood; and planning and project information.
Community development; Medford Campus; Medford/Somerville history; Chinatown; Boston Campus; Tufts Campus Buildings; University Relations; Facilities; Medford/Somerville history; Greater Boston history
- Project files, 1921 -- 2018; 1970 -- 2016; UA233.001; 9.2 Linear Feet 8 record cartons, 2 letter size document boxes, and 2 oversize folders
  Conditions Governing Access
  University records are closed for 20 years from the date of creation. Records older than 20 years that do not pertain to student education, staff and faculty employment and Board of Trustees records are open for research.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Transferred by the Office of Community Relations, 2013-2018.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged in received order.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains files relating to construction and other projects at Tufts sites and buildings. Files include construction and architechture plans and maps; proposals; permits and licenses; studies and reports; correspondence; publicity and neighborhood communications; and files on committees, including meeting minutes and agendas.
  - Royall House Stamp - First Issue, 1990 June 16; UA233.001.001.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Open for research.
  - Royall House Reporter (The Middlesex Canal 1793-1860), 1973 January; UA233.001.001.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Lifting the Veil - Remembering the Burning of the Ursuline Convent exhibition, 1997 June; UA233.001.001.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Hobbs Building and Somerville Theater analysis, circa 1983; UA233.001.001.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Tufts Magazine, Summer 1984, UA233.001.001.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Publications, 1921, 1935, 1938, 1984, 1988, 1994 -- 1995, 2002; UA233.001.001.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Somerville's Last Frontier (Mystic View site) Community Forum, 1999 May 22; UA233.001.001.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Friends of Seven Hills Park Collaborative, 1998 September; UA233.001.001.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Tufts University Biomedical Research and Nutrition Complex, draft impact report, 1996 September 3; UA233.001.001.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Tufts University Biomedical Research and Nutrition Complex, final impact report, 1997 January; UA233.001.001.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Anderson Hall and Bray Laboratory Addendum, 1984 February 10; UA233.001.001.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Davis Square Action Plan, 1984; UA233.001.001.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - New Athletics Complex Magazine, circa 1976 -- 1992; UA233.001.001.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Proposed zoning and planning changes in Somerville and Medford, 1988 February 19; UA233.001.001.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Alumni Council Member Directory, 2000 -- 2001; UA233.001.001.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 15)
    20 years from date of creation.
  - Tufts University School of Medicine Directory of Faculty Research Strengths, circa 1984 -- 1990; UA233.001.001.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - New Century Policies - Local Initiatives for Affordable Housing, 1988 December 7; UA233.001.001.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Changes in Somerville's Housing Market report, 1986 May; UA233.001.001.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Well being of Somerville Health Agenda report, 2002 -- 2003; UA233.001.001.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Domestic Violence in Somerville report, 1995 September 27; UA233.001.001.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Aberjona River Commission draft report, 1971 February 22; UA233.001.001.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Mystic River Watershed Symposium report, circa 1970 -- 1975; UA233.001.001.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Environmental Quality of the Mystic River Basin report, 1970 December; UA233.001.001.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Aberjona River Commission - Establishment and Operation report, circa 1970; UA233.001.001.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - High School Teacher of the Year Awards from current Tufts students, 1991; UA233.001.001.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - M.A.S.T. Program/U.S. DOE grant proposal, 1991 May; UA233.001.001.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Teacher programs, 1982 -- 1989; UA233.001.001.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - C.E.T.A. Summer program, 1973 -- 1983; UA233.001.001.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - 21st Century School grant, 2004; UA233.001.001.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Total Quality Schools report, 1992; UA233.001.001.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Joint educational collaborative project between Somerville and Tufts proposal, 1985 January 4; UA233.001.001.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Project Teach/Y2K, 2000 March 7; UA233.001.001.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Somerville Early Childhood Education Council grant, 1996; UA233.001.001.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - All America City in Tampa presentation, 2008 April 24; UA233.001.001.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Brewster Library: Cape Cod Portraits by G.H. Ballou, 2003; UA233.001.001.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - SAED program, 1996; UA233.001.001.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - The New Diasporas Conference, 1994; UA233.001.001.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - WMFO Radio Station, 1986 -- 1992; UA233.001.001.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Tufts Student Organizations Volunteer Effort sampling, 1988; UA233.001.001.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Tufts Community Gardens agreement, 1975 April 4; UA233.001.001.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Tufts Shuttle Bus Correspondence, 1972; UA233.001.001.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Public Service Task Force proposal, 1995 January 9; UA233.001.001.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - New Communications Technologies Fund requests, 1984 January 9; UA233.001.001.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Liberal Arts Students Summer Jobs Pilot programs, 1984 January 9; UA233.001.001.00044; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - MA Historic Landscape Preservation Grant/Milk Row Cemetery, 2001 May 15; UA233.001.001.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Tufts Environmental Studies Majors scholarships, 1999; UA233.001.001.00046; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - W.K. Kellogg Foundation Grant for Eliot-Pearson Dept. of Child Development, 1997; UA233.001.001.00047; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Voluntary Service Award Grant - After School Project for Haitian Children, 1996 June 28; UA233.001.001.00048; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Challenge grants for Technology in Education, 1996; UA233.001.001.00049; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - NEH grant application - Somerville CIS, 1995; UA233.001.001.00050; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Building Community Health through Partnerships grant proposal, 1994; UA233.001.001.00051; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Child Study Department grant proposal, 1990; UA233.001.001.00052; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Medford Chamber of Commerce analysis, 1968; UA233.001.002.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Tufts Commuter Rail Stop, 1970 -- 1980; UA233.001.002.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Eliot-Pearson Dept./Center for Reading Research - Boston Reading Intervention project, circa 1996; UA233.001.002.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Special Commission on Tax Reform - Research proposal to Commonwealth of MA, 1980 -- 1989; UA233.001.002.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Tufts University - A Guide to Living Off-Campus, circa 2010 -- 2018; UA233.001.002.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Tufts Community Day, 2016; UA233.001.002.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Tufts in the Community - Neighbors partners, circa 2015; UA233.001.002.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Engines of Economic Growth: Economic Impact of Boston's Eight Research Universities on Boston, 2003; UA233.001.002.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Hobbs Building and Davis Square report, circa 1983; UA233.001.002.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Environmental Health investigation at Tufts Administration Building, 2001 November; UA233.001.002.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Community Service proposals, 2002; UA233.001.002.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Active Citizenship and Service to Society reflective essays, 1999 November; UA233.001.002.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Solar House, 2008 -- 2009; UA233.001.002.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Tufts Management Program for Community Organizations draft proposal, 1983 June; UA233.001.002.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Steering Committee Retreat - Tufts College of Citizenship and Public Service, 2000 July 26; UA233.001.003.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Tufts University Summer of Service Magazine, 1993; UA233.001.003.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - "Lives of Active Citizenship" - Robert M. Hollister Inaugural Talk, 2002 February 7; UA233.001.003.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - The Future of Boston Area Nonprofits report, 1998 July; UA233.001.003.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Somerville Performing Arts Center, 1980 -- 1984; UA233.001.003.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Redline NW Market Demand report, 1977; UA233.001.003.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The Healey School Playground Project, 1988 May; UA233.001.003.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Somerville Theatre as a Performing Arts Center proposal, 1980 December 15; UA233.001.SB147.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box Shared 147, Folder 7)
  - Tufts Community Day flier, 2016; UA233.001.SB147.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box Shared 147, Folder 8)
  - Bello Field Construction, 2004; UA233.001.014.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 1)
    Civil War
  - Cabot/Cabot Daycare, 1989; UA233.001.014.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Campus Center, 1981 -- 1983; UA233.001.014.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Cabot, 1979; UA233.001.014.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Campus Center, continued, 1983 -- 1987; UA233.001.014.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Campus Planning, 1981; UA233.001.014.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Campus environment issues, 1988; UA233.001.014.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Campus Development, 1981 -- 1982; UA233.001.014.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Campus Development Committee, 1983; UA233.001.014.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Campus Development Committee, 1984; UA233.001.014.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Campus Development Committee, 1985; UA233.001.014.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Articles for Campus Development Committee, 1983; UA233.001.014.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Campus Development Committee, 1986 -- 1987; UA233.001.014.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Campus Development Committee Proceedings, 1981 -- 1989; UA233.001.014.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Center for Environmental Management (CEM), 1988 -- 1994; UA233.001.014.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Carmichael Dining Hall Renovations, 1993, 2004; UA233.001.014.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Capen House, Tufts University, 2012; UA233.001.014.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - 4 Colby Street, 1988 -- 1991, 2001 -- 2003; UA233.001.014.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Colby Street Part 2, 1986 -- 1989; UA233.001.014.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - College Ave Bridge, 1981 -- 1996; UA233.001.014.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Eliot Pearson Childcare, 1981 -- 1991; UA233.001.014.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Construction - MHEFA Funding, 1991, 1995; UA233.001.015.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Cousens Gym, 1993 -- 1996; UA233.001.015.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Tufts - Field House, 1998 -- 1999; UA233.001.015.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Fieldhouse/Garage, 1989, 1998 -- 2000; UA233.001.015.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Powderhouse proposal development, 2009 -- 2013; UA233.001.015.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Powderhouse Boulevard Gate, 1993 -- 1994; UA233.001.015.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Psychology building, 1999 -- 2000; UA233.001.015.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - O.P.C.D., 1984 -- 1987; UA233.001.015.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Noisy Building Ordinance Boston, 1992; UA233.001.015.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - New England Medical Center, 1983, 1993; UA233.001.015.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Step Up, 2009 -- 2012; UA233.001.015.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Construction -- Somerville, 2004; UA233.001.015.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - TAB (Tufts Administration Building)/OSHA, 1998 -- 1999; UA233.001.015.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - TAB (Tufts Administration Building)/OSHA, 1995 -- 1997; UA233.001.015.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Zoning - Medford, 1991 -- 1992, 1998; UA233.001.016.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Zoning 2 - Medford, 1982 -- 1983, 1990; UA233.001.016.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Zoning 3 - Medford Dover Amendment, 1989 -- 1994; UA233.001.016.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Hillside dorm project, 1978 -- 1979; UA233.001.016.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - College Ave dorm project, 1978 -- 1980, 1989; UA233.001.016.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Housing Policy Council/Halligan project letters, 1986, 2004; UA233.001.016.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Hillel Center, 1993 -- 1994; UA233.001.016.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Medford Garage, 1986 -- 1989, 1998; UA233.001.016.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Medford Garage 2, 1996 -- 1998; UA233.001.016.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Home Rule petitions, 1985 -- 1986, 1989, 1991; UA233.001.016.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Jaharis, 1997 -- 2000; UA233.001.017.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Jaharis 2, 2000 -- 2001; UA233.001.017.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Jaharis Project BRA, 1991 -- 1998; UA233.001.017.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Latin Way dorm, 1978 -- 1981; UA233.001.017.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Mass Historical Commission, 2004; UA233.001.017.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - MBTA/Davis Square, 1980, 1984 -- 1987; UA233.001.017.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Medford Hillside Business Association, 1980, 1989; UA233.001.017.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Medford land court, 1989 -- 1991; UA233.001.017.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - MDC Boathouse, 1985 -- 1987; UA233.001.017.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Medford skating rink, 1982, 1986, 1989; UA233.001.017.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Mural project, 1991 -- 1992; UA233.001.017.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Mystic Ave - Center for Waste Management (1), 1983 -- 1987; UA233.001.017.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Mystic Ave - Center for Waste Management (2), 1983 -- 1987; UA233.001.017.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Tufts Administration Building, 1986 -- 1987, 2006; UA233.001.018.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Tufts Administration Building, 1986 -- 1987, 2006; UA233.001.018.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Boathouse - Malden River Part 2, 2004 -- 2005; UA233.001.018.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Boathouse - Malden River, 2005; UA233.001.018.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Green Line, 1984, 2000 -- 2003; UA233.001.018.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Green Line Project (1), 2004; UA233.001.018.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Green Line Project (2), 2004; UA233.001.018.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Green Line Project (1), 2005; UA233.001.018.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Green Line Project (2), 2005; UA233.001.018.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Green Line Project (1), 2006; UA233.001.018.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Green Line Project (2), 2006; UA233.001.018.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Green Line Project, 2007; UA233.001.018.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Green Line Project 2008A, UA233.001.018.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Green Line Project 2008B, UA233.001.019.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Green Line Project 2009A, UA233.001.019.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Green Line Project 2009B (1), UA233.001.019.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Green Line Project 2009B (2), UA233.001.019.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Green Line Project 2010A, UA233.001.019.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Green Line Project 2010B (1), UA233.001.019.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Green Line Project 2010B (2), UA233.001.019.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Green Line Project (1), 2011; UA233.001.019.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Green Line Project (2), 2011; UA233.001.019.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Green Line Extension Project, 2014; UA233.001.019.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Green Line Extension Project 2, 2009 -- 2016; UA233.001.019.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Green Line Extension Project 2, 2009 -- 2016; UA233.001.019.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - TAB (Tufts Administration Building) - Western Jr. High, 1986 -- 1988, 2000 -- 2002; UA233.001.020.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - TAB (Tufts Administration Building) - Western Jr. High (2), 1986 -- 1988, 2000 -- 2002; UA233.001.020.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - TAB (Tufts Administration Building) (1), 1997 -- 2001; UA233.001.020.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - TAB (Tufts Administration Building) (2), 1997 -- 2001; UA233.001.020.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Powderhouse proposal, 2013 -- 2014; UA233.001.020.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - TAB (Tufts Administration Building) - Western Jr. High part 2, 1984 -- 1986, 2000 -- 2004; UA233.001.020.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - TAB (Tufts Administration Building) - Western Jr. High part 2, 1984 -- 1986, 2000 -- 2004; UA233.001.020.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Taxation, 1971 -- 1980; UA233.001.020.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Townscape - Medford, 1984; UA233.001.020.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Grafton State Hospital, 1992 -- 1993; UA233.001.020.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Tot Lot, 1973, 1985, 1989 -- 1991; UA233.001.020.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Tisch Wessell Extension, 1982, 1994; UA233.001.020.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Wellington Circle - Mystic Ave (1), 1982 -- 1987; UA233.001.020.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Wellington Circle - Mystic Ave (2), 1982 -- 1987; UA233.001.020.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Powderhouse School, 2013 -- 2014; UA233.001.020.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Teele Square Planning - Real Estate Analysis, 2009; UA233.001.020.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Subject files, 1971 -- 2016; UA233.002; 7.5 Linear Feet 7 record cartons and 1 letter size document box